Inari Expedition! Inari Expedition!
That's all for now, Groundstylast, Inari and Stardacher, thank you very much.
I am Heng Tachibanako.
I am Rinu Tamimi.
Please, please.
What I would like you two to do today is this.
Today's exploration is an episode talk, a scavenger hunt!
Wow! I've never heard that before!
First time you've heard it?
I'm sure it's the first time I've said that.
What kind of exploration is this?
There are various stores in the E Beans building.
There are various shops in the E Beans building, and there are staff members there.
And when you two appear in live performances or on TV, you often talk about episodes of your lives, right?
They often talk about episodes in their live performances or on TV.
Often, comedians would say things like, "My manager did this to me.
or "my manager" or "my junior staff did this and that.
They would talk about episodes.
They would tell interesting stories about people they know.
That's what we are going to do today.
So you are going to get them today?
Yes! I mean, from the staff working at E Beans.
Borrow an episodic talk from a staff member who works at E Beans.
I see!
Then come back here and talk about it as if it were your own episodic talk.
But when I say episodic talk, I mean like a non-slip story.
It would be too hard.
Any genre is fine.
There are stories about love flowers, your biggest failure, and so on.
We will borrow a story that makes a big impression and present it to you.
So let's get going!
One, two, go!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
All alone! In one!
Please give me a high rating if you found it helpful!
Which one would you like to try next time...?
Please leave a comment!
Okay, we're both back.
Did you get it? Episodes
Borrowed it.
Oh, I'm so excited!
I'm so excited!
Well, I'm going to ask you to show us the episodes you rented.
Which one shall we start with?
Let's see...
I'll go first.
Really?
Please do.
Let's hear the first episode from the Kitami group.
The first story I borrowed is...
Happening in America.
Sounds interesting.
Africa?
America.
You put an American story in here for a good film?
That's amazing.
At this point, it's really starting to make an impact.
Yeah, it's great.
I'm going on a trip to America.
I'm so excited.
I'm so excited!
But I'm Japanese, so I don't speak English.
It's my first time there, so I don't know the way.
I don't know everything!
In this day and age, if you have a smart phone, you can do everything.
It translates for you.
And it can give me directions.
It's a great help when you're in trouble, isn't it?
But you know what?
I lost my smartphone in the U.S.
That sucks!
I'm in a bad mood all day long
All in a day's work
It was the worst trip to the U.S.
That's it!
Aaaaah!
I'm really curious to know what happened after that.
By the way, this is
This is for the manager of the muscle store.
Ooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!
I don't have such a screwed up image.
I wonder what happens after that.
I wonder what will happen after that.
I'm curious about the sequel.
I'm curious.
I wonder how they got through it.
If you're curious about the rest of the story, go to the muscle store and
Do your shopping.
And while you're waiting for your meal, you can listen to the rest of the story.
It's a bonus.
Okay. Thank you.
That's wonderful.
Next, Ms. Kai, please.
Okay, I'll go.
This is...
This is about an acquaintance of mine.
Very nice.
This one was in the bathtub.This was in the bathtub, apparently.
The acquaintance said...
When he was taking a bath, the water was very hot.
I screamed, "It's so hot!
And a friend of his came over and asked him what happened.
He asked me what was wrong.
I told him it was too hot and asked him to adjust the temperature.
He said it was too hot and asked her to adjust the temperature.
My friend said okay, so I took out the hot water.
So he tried to pour out the hot water, but it was cold.
So he got angry and said it was too cold.
Then my friend said, "Come with me.
And then his friend heard that and said that his friend's water was colder than his water.
That's so good!
Like a rakugo story.
It's like a rakugo story, but with a really strong ending.
You got it right.
It was great!
By the way...
This is Mr. Mackie with the nice earphones.
Looks like...
Mr. Mackie is from Osaka.
Oh, yes.
That was as expected
That was fun.
It was good.
Let's move on to the second one.
The second one I'm interested in is
The big proposal!
Wow! A love story!
A love story?
Well, we'll be talking about it in our very own research!
Oh, it's going to be fun!
First, a guy fell in love with a girl in middle school.
It starts in middle school.
The innocent one had a crush on her.
In the ninth grade.
It's time to say goodbye.
Sure enough, the boy takes the plunge and confesses his love to the girl.
I like you.
Please go out with me
I'm sorry.
What?
You're going to reject me?
But I'm still in middle school.
It's not that big of a shock.
I've managed to turn things around and move on with my life.
I've moved on with my life.
Started to move on?
Another step.
When I was in high school.
Something happened.
Oh, my God?
A girl called me.
What?
She was a girl I'd confessed to in junior high.
I confessed my feelings to her.
No way, right? How is that possible?
I'm so excited.
The girl...
One word.
I like you.
And the boy?
I'm sorry.
Oh, I know you are.
You're an idiot, you're an idiot.
What?
Why, why, why?
Why? Why? I don't get it.
What are you switching?
What? What? Why are you switching?
What do you mean? You're feeling unstable.
First you eat like this, then you go to high school, then you dump her.
And then you're in high school, and then you dump her, and then you're in high school, and then you dump her again.
It's been a while.
I happened to meet this woman at a store.
We bumped into each other.
That's amazing.
We struck up a conversation, and after a while, we started dating.
What? What? What?
Who told you that? I'm really curious.
Three shows.
I'm curious.
The man is purely interested in the relationship, and the man confesses... no, no, no...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no?
Confession...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Gaijin? American story?
Lost phone?
I decided to propose, not confess.
Oh, finally, this time it's a man's proposal.
It's a proposal, so I thought I'd better do it right.
I invited the woman to dreamland.
I invited her to Mouse Land.
Oh!
Speaking of Mousetrap Land.
I'm going to propose in front of the castle.
That's nice, isn't it?
Okay, nice nice.
Men, plan well.Men should plan well.
I went to Mouse Land with a woman I was dating.
That's nice.
But the place to go that he should have been prepared for.
Ah!
It didn't happen in time.
What?
You couldn't make it in time?
If I had ordered it, I would have had it made.
You mean it didn't arrive by the day you were going to propose?
That's not good.
But we didn't have to argue yet.
I was thinking about getting the glass slipper ready.
I'm still in love with you.
But...
We didn't make it in time.
But I thought if I had the feelings, and if I proposed in front of a castle like that...
Somehow I realized that we were sitting on a bench together, no rings, no balas shoes.
Just a bench and ask me to marry you.
That was OK, but I felt kind of sad and kind of happy.
It was with these mixed feelings that my great love affair got off to a great start!
Lovely!
The proposal was a success, and you're married.
So much has happened!
It really is a great love affair.
What?
Big love.
I was wrong.
Who is this great love of yours, by the way?
Maru-chan from Ehlins.
Maruchan?
From Mr. Haruyama.
That's romantic.
Amazing, isn't it?
I have so many questions.
I'm curious why you dumped me once in high school.
I'm curious.
It bothers me a lot.
It's quite a miracle that he confessed to you in junior high and then confessed to you in high school.
It's amazing, isn't it?
We met again at a store when I was around 20, we started dating, and then we went to Disney.
Fingers don't get in time and glass shoes don't get in time, that's obviously the plan.
I mean, you're a girly-girly-eater.
I don't think that's the kind of thing that happens in the Erin's business.
Maybe, just maybe, it's Maru-chan's fault.
I don't want the paychecks not being transferred.
Maru-chan, Maru-chan.
You can't say that.
I can't afford to miss a paycheck.
We'll lose our livelihood.
That's great. It's amazing, being a high school student in middle school.
It's adorable, all those episodes.
It's a mistake.
When you come to Erin's.
If I see you at an event or something.
I'll give you a "ha-ha" if I see you at an event or something.
That way? Dreamland.
It reminds you of that, doesn't it?
Poor little girl.
That was a great episode.
It was tough.
Okay, high school.
I have a love story, too.
You got a love story.
Here's a love story... and a love story back.
I'm looking forward to it.
I wonder what it's about.
This is a story about a person who has been a good friend of mine.
She's working at E-Beans now.
Before this job, she was working at an apparel store.
This apparel store?
She worked at the Sendai store.
There was also a main store.
There was a women's main store.
The women's main store had a very cute
I heard that there was a very pretty
I heard that there was a very pretty woman in the women's main store, who was often featured in magazines.
I see... it's the same company, but she's from the head office.
She's from the head office of the same company
She's from the head office of the same company.
She's beautiful.
When I saw her...
From the first moment I saw her.
I fell in love with her.
I've been admiring her ever since.
Ever since I admired her.
I really wanted to get close to him.
I really want to be close to him.
She worked extremely hard at her job.
She stocked up on clothes every day.
Stocking up on clothes?
Not on your own?
You worked hard?
I wanted her to recognize me.
That's right.
I've been transferred to headquarters.
Thanks to your hard work.
I've been recognized.
I'm going to the head office.
Then, there was this person.
That person...That's the person.
So that's where it starts.
That's where the appeal starts.
But this person...
I heard that the woman was a very strong drinker.
I knew someone who was a very strong drinker.
My acquaintance is a very weak drinker.
I see.
Because she's a weak drinker.
I thought to myself...
I was with a woman who guzzled.
I'll put them together.
Isn't that the story?
I'm still a little hungover.
He went out to dinner with her.
They even went to Dreamland.
They went out to eat many times.
And when they went to dreamland...
I confessed my feelings to him.
In dreamland?
That's right.
What?
The man who confessed...
The man I know now...
Is now his wife!
It worked!
So you got together with a guy from your company, and you even got married?
They are married and have been together for about 10 years now.
That's amazing!
So it's like dating someone you like.
That's true.
I want curry! Go for it!
If you go to the house!
Stop, stop, stop!
Who are you talking about? Isn't that Mr. Mallefer?
I think I've heard of him.
This is a video of Mr. Suda from Rooftop E-Garden.
He's so handsome!
He looks cool, but such a romantic.
I heard he liked it a lot.
He had so much heat.
I wouldn't mind coming over to that guy at all.
I wouldn't mind at all!
Because he has big hands and he's handsome.
He's so cool.
But you did your best. I think your hard work has been received.
So, in a manner of speaking, you are now in Tokyo, married, and coming to Sendai for the two of you?
Yes, that's right. Bring them back.
Bring her back?
Aren't you Princess Peach?
Why is she trapped in the radiation of Tokyo?
Isn't she the brave one?
I see.
I'd like to see that.
All kinds of people work here, EV.
That's for sure. Everyone's a human being.
I want to hear their love stories again.
I want to hear it!
This is the kind of love she's in.
I want to hear it! I want to do it!
Let's all go to Martena together.
Really?
It's like a discussion.
Discussion?
Interesting!
Let's go to the third one.
This was a mistake at a drinking party.
Drinking party?
When you grow up, you have boyfriends, so that kind of thing.
I see.
A man.
The man.
I went to a drinking party with all the employees.
Oh!
And we were drinking and having a good time.
I want to go back to come
I thought it was cute and came to the top.
Some men, like this, stand up to add to their intoxication when they add to their intoxication.
That's right. To whom?
I wondered if it was okay for me to say that.
Everyone else is made to do it sitting down, but me.
A little bit.
You know, there is a man who sits down and adds to his drunkenness.
That man is the kind of person who always gets drunk sitting down, in my opinion.
I'm totally there.
Well, then, I'm looking at them.
So, at the restaurant, I went into a private room and added to his intoxication.
I had to be patient because the conversation was pretty lively.
So I went in there pretty much at the last minute.
Oh, I felt refreshed and opened the door.
Then I saw a foreign woman standing in front of me.
What?
The man was confused.
Let's just get out! When he opened the door, he saw many women standing in line.
He sobered up at once.
Gah! Oh no!
That was the story. I see.
I was a little drunk, and I was in a hurry because I didn't think I would make it in time.
I was in a hurry because I didn't think I was going to make it in time, so I went into the women's restroom without checking.I also went into the women's restroom without checking.
I'm probably a sit-down drunk, so I didn't realize if I was in the women's restroom or the men's restroom.
I see. You even take a glance there.
Can I ask you this? Who are we talking about? I don't know. Can I ask you this?
One wrong move and we're talking about a pervert.
Certainly.
This is for Mr. Kyoro of Mr. In-ya-phone.
Eeeee!
He's a little bit, you know, cute.
She had an atmosphere that seemed to cool down with alcohol.
Actually!
That's not true!
I'm talking about whether she was really drunk or not! Mr. Kyoro!
Mr. Kyoro!
I think you meant it in a questioning way, didn't you? This.
Kyoro-san!
I'm so shocked.
I'm in a hurry. That's what I'm talking about.
Maybe he left with his earphones in.
Like you can't hear anything around you.
I see.
Can I have the third one from Kanae-san, please?
This is also a story from a person who has been a good friend of mine.
It's an episode of a "bummer".
It seems that she has a favorite group.
One day, he went to Tokyo to see a live concert of his favorite group.
After seeing the show, he was in a wonderful and happy mood.
Then he had a drink and was even happier.
I was like, "I'm so happy to be alive.
I looked at my phone.
There were only 2 minutes left until the time of the night bus I was supposed to take.
That's when I knew I was in trouble.
I ran as fast as I could.
The night bus seemed to have gone right in front of me.
That was the worst.
I thought, "This is the worst.
But then I got another one.
But there was another one, a late one from a different site.
There was still time, so I made a reservation for the night bus.
I had some time until then, so I thought, "Let's go have a few more drinks.
So we went out for a drink.
Delicious. It was cool. The drinks are good.
It tastes good, that's what drinking is all about.
That's right.
It's bad.
I'm happy like that.
And then I glanced at my cell phone, and it said, "Oh shit, three minutes ago.
What are you doing?
I run, and the night bus arrives.
It's leaving right in front of me.
What are you doing? It's leaving.
But it's no good, so we decide to go back the next day.
I gave up that day.
So we booked a bus.
I stayed at the hotel, went to bed, and by the time I woke up, the bus was leaving.
Three times?
I was hungover.
Oh no.
So, I told him that I was planning to go to Osaka again.
He said he would take a plane then.
It's just a matter of time, so it's OK.
With alcohol?
Whose is this, by the way?
This is Mr. Hayasaka of HMV.
I see.
The lady with the blue hair.
I'm talking about the lady with blue hair.
She's making a mistake with alcohol.
She seems cute.
I was the first to hear about it, so I'm pretty vague about it.
But don't you have that kind of thing, too?
No, um, really.
It's not a drinking mistake.
I was just thinking, she didn't have any alcohol in her system.
I've seen her fail to get on a bus.
That's right.
She was excited to go to Tokyo by herself to have something to look forward to.
It's really hard for us to be this excited.
So, I really hope she has a good time.
We went using Tohoku-san's UQ, which is only available for one day.
That's how much she was looking forward to it.
We also asked them how they liked it. We even asked each other how we liked it.
But we couldn't get on the bus.
What was the reason?
There is a deeper reason.
My fun let's go time was over that day, too.
There is a waiting room at the bus stop, right?
I arrived there about 4 hours before.
That's too early.
But it was a night bus to take.
I thought it would be a bad idea to go out at night.
So I waited in the waiting room for a long time.
I waited in the waiting room for about four hours.
Then I thought it was time to get on the bus.
When I went to the bus stop, there was no bus.
The bus that was supposed to be there was not there. It didn't have a name.
I asked, "Where is this bus? I asked.
I asked where it was, and was told that it was a little further down the road.
After about 2 minutes, I knew I was in trouble.
I was carrying all kinds of baggage.
I got out, but the train left right in front of me.I had already escaped, but the car departed right in front of me.
I was crying and called my parents.
I called my manager, and he got me a hotel nearby.
You saved me, didn't you?
That's right. They helped me.
We decided to take the early morning bus.
When I woke up in the morning, it was three minutes before the bus.
We are exactly the same.
That's right. So I just gathered all my stuff and headed for the bus.
I couldn't make it in time, so I called the captain.
I called the captain, and he said, "Oh, okay," and got me a flight.
We flew back.
You wanted to fly home, didn't you?
I was with the staff after all.
You missed the flight and ended up flying home.
Yes, that's true.
I could have a chip or GPS implanted in me.
I really think so.
GPS.
I'm serious.
Cells as idols.
It's possible.
Is that all?
Yes, that's all.
I've borrowed a lot of stories from the waiter.
I think it would be good to have their stories, too.
Sure, I'm sure.
Well, I don't mind if you start from either side.
I'd like to hear one of your episodic talks.
I'll tell you my story.
The incident took place...
Here.
Backstage at E-Bee's.
I had an event at E-Bee's in the summer.
event
I was told that we were going to have a live concert at E-Bee's.
I've always taken care of them.
This dressing room is like a home for us.
So this dressing room is like a home for me.
This dressing room is like a home to me.
That's why I'm doing this.
We do our own hair.
We set our own hair.
Hair.
I'm especially sore around here.
Mm-hmm.
But it does burn, just a little bit.
Oh.
Actually, I had one this morning.
What?
You get burned?
Recently?
I got a burn this morning, too.
And it's a really small burn, so...
I don't know what's going on.
I'm used to it.
It's just a little burn.
Really.
I get burned about once every three days.
Oh, that's disgusting.
So I'm good with burns, but...
Just that one day.
I'll use an iron to curl my hair.
Tofuku-san's common T-shirt
On the day of the zecchini shorts outfit
I dropped it on my thigh.
And I had to endure a lot of pain
I'm not the type to show my emotions
But it hurt a little too much.
I got all willy willy willy.
But I had to go to a scoring session.
That was before you went.
Well, I figured it was too late for that.
So I did the OK treatment anyway.
But there was a pretty big cosmetic tear.
It was all taped up.
So I wrapped a towel around it and covered it up.
And a member of the scoring group with me
He wrapped a towel around me
so that it didn't look like an injury.
I was in a lot of pain and I was in a lot of pain and I was in a lot of pain.
I kind of got over it.
It was pretty big.
It's gonna stay, it's gonna be bad.
I'm a believer in Kizu Power Pad.
I'm a big believer in them.
When I was in elementary school, I had an injury on my glasses.
I healed it with Kizu Power Pad without going to the hospital.
I really believe in it.
That's why I decided to put on Kizu Power Pad.
I'm going to put it on as soon as I get home.
I've been spending a lot of time.
You've been wearing Kizu Power Pad for a few days.
You put it on for a few days, right?
When I decided to change it once...
It didn't heal well.It's not quite healed.
This is pretty much the size of it.
It's a burn of about this size.
On my thigh.
Your wife wears a lot of shorts.
I thought we should go to the hospital.
So we went to a dermatologist.
To treat the burns at the dermatologist's office.
I had to peel off the Kizu Power Pad
And then...
I peeled it off with a plop
I found a Roman alphabet engraved on it.
Roman letters?
Like AR.
I don't remember.
I'm a little fuzzy.
Let's say it's AER.
It's inscribed with Roman letters like AER.
What?
I don't know.
I'm like an alien or something.
What?
It's like Banks was carved into it.
And then the doctor at the hospital...
I've been thinking about it a lot.
It's carved into the iron.
It's all smashed up.
The letters that are sticking out.
From the burns.
What? !
It's like an indentation.
Oh!
That's what I thought.
I couldn't get it off.
I thought it would really stay as AR.
But they gave me some medicine.
Kizu Power Pads...
I put it on.
I spent some time with it.
And it healed to some extent.
That AR won't go away.
So you go to school and wear skirts.
When you go to school and wear skirts...
I can see a little bit.
White letters on my thighs.
My friends said...
They said, "That's nice, it looks like a tattoo.
Like it's fashionable.
It's been there for about six months.
Oh, my God!
So I felt like it was a tattoo.
I thought I'd have to live with it for the rest of my life.
I thought it would stay like that for the rest of my life.
But now the scar is gone.
I left the letters "AR" on my thigh
AR on my thigh
I lived with the letters AR on my thighs for 6 months.
That happened?
Yes, it did.
You have to be careful.
It's a relay.
Even burns are fashionable.
It's a pain in the ass.
What a pain in the ass.
It's like, "Hey, it's a tattoo!
I'm the type of person who's afraid of people around me.
That's how I feel.
So it just faded away?
It's gone.
I'm so glad.
And Kizper Apad.
That's what you're trying to say.
I'm just trying to say "kiz per apad.
If I didn't have the Kizper a Pad, I wouldn't be in Starr's.
I really hurt my face once.
Kiz-per-a-pad.
I'm just saying.
Hey...
I was...
When I went to Aomori
I had a live concert in Aomori for your story.
On that day...
332? I was a member of
We were divided into different rooms.
It was a rather early night.
We were like, "Let's go to bed early.
Let's go to bed early.
I was a member of the group.
They were very energetic.
Let's go to bed early
We were a team
I went to bed early.
Then I woke up in the middle of the night
I woke up in the middle of the night.
I went outside quietly.
I went out into the hallway.
I decided to buy some water.
I bought some water.
I was going to go back in.I tried to go back in.
The door wouldn't open.
I was like, "What's going on?
I need your key card.
Like a credit card.
Like a loyalty card.
A credit card.
It costs money to get in every time.
It's like a loyalty card.
I couldn't open it.
I thought it was a bad idea.
I called a few times.
I'm sorry, but I tried.
But I couldn't get through.
I don't know what to do.
I was strolling the hallway
I was strolling the hallways looking for a way in.
There was a card booth or something like that.
Like a card booth.
They sell room keys.
Idiots.
I was about to buy one.
I was going to buy one, but the card was a little dangerous.
I know what you mean.
I thought it was a bad idea.
Before I bought it.
I went to the lobby and got the card.
And I was able to get some sleep.
I usually go to the front desk first.
I don't know.
I'm going to look for it, aren't I?
If they sell key cards in the hallway...
Useless.
I'm just wondering if there's something in there.
The wrong person...
I don't know.
At the time, I was...
I was sleepy, so maybe I wasn't thinking straight.
I thought maybe they were selling cards.
I thought maybe...
I stopped.
You keep saying you missed the express pass earlier.
And now you're saying it's because you were sleepy.
Maybe he's been drinking.
You've been drinking.
It's like he's having a memory-dumping episode.
It's like he's having an episode as a memory jog.
Was it water?
It was lemon soda.
I'd be careful.
You know, moto locks...
It's a common occurrence.
I didn't open it.
You two are funny.
Hard to put a coat on.
Really?
This is the episode I got from you.
They're all good, aren't they?
You guys are funny.
There's the waitress.
I guess that's what you call e-beaning.
I'm sure there's more where that came from.
I'm sure there's more.
I'd love to.
Bring it in here.
I want to do it.
Let's all sizzle with the iron.
Walk.
Before we start talking.
AER.
Let's all wrap up in towels.
I want to do it.
Okay, I'll be right back.
We were able to borrow a lot of episodes this time.
If we can do a second one...
Let's do it.
I was looking at E Beans.
I've got one.
I'll tell you myself.
I'll be waiting for you in the comments.
I'd love to be on it.
I have more episodes like this.
I'd love to hear more.
We'd love to hear from you.
High for this kind of personality
from the people who work here.
Please come and visit us!
We're waiting for you.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.
See you soon.
E Beans